<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pure Leagues</string>
    <!--<string name="parse_server_url">http://parse-env.3ckhcpskac.us-east-1.elasticbeanstalk.com/parse</string>-->
    <string name="parse_server_url">http://parse-env.3ckhcpskac.us-east-1.elasticbeanstalk.com/parse</string>
    <string name="parse_app_id">72C6FFA9CF4C2</string>

    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-3091183191433381~7884222551</string>
    <string name="admob_app_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3091183191433381/3314422154</string>

    <string name="login_screen_title">Welcome to Pure Leagues</string>
    <string name="welcome_screen_subtitle">The essential sporting app for following your favourite team.</string>
    <string name="welcome_login_button_text">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_add_team_button_text">Add a team</string>
    <string name="yes_text">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_text">No</string>
    <string name="welcome_register_subtitle_text">Would you like to register first to have access to all features?</string>
    <string name="username_hint">Username</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="login_forgot_pass_text">Forgotten password?</string>
    <string name="submit_button_text">Submit</string>
    <string name="login_password_recovery_hint">Enter your email address below and we will email you a link to change your password.</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Email address</string>
    <string name="registration_screen_title">Registration</string>
    <string name="name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="registration_email_hint">Email</string>
    <string name="confirm_password_hint">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="continue_button_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth_hint">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="gender_hint">Gender</string>
    <string name="user_type_hint">Type of user</string>
    <string name="male_item">Male</string>
    <string name="female_item">Female</string>
    <string name="player_item">Player</string>
    <string name="manager_item">Manager</string>
    <string name="referee_item">Referee</string>
    <string name="family_member_item">Family Member</string>
    <string name="follower_item">Follower</string>
    <string name="complete_registration_button_text">Complete registration</string>
    <string name="register_continue_title_text">Complete the following to select your favourite team to follow in Pure Leagues</string>
    <string name="football_association_hint">Choose your football association</string>
    <string name="club_hint">Club name</string>
    <string name="division_hint">Division</string>
    <string name="team_colors_hint">Select team colours</string>
    <string name="register_button_text">Register</string>
    <string name="football_association">Football association</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search</string>
    <string name="team_colors_title">Team Colours</string>
    <string name="tab_fixtures_title">Fixtures</string>
    <string name="tab_results_title">Results</string>
    <string name="tab_tables_title">Tables</string>
    <string name="tab_stats_title">Stats</string>
    <string name="tab_gallery_title">Gallery</string>
    <string name="tab_calendar_title">Calendar</string>
    <string name="username_empty_error_message">Username cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="username_min_length_error_message">Username must be a minimum of %d characters</string>
    <string name="password_empty_error_message">Please enter password</string>
    <string name="password_min_length_error_message">Password must be a minimum of %d characters and include letters and numbers</string>
    <string name="name_empty_error_message">Name is empty</string>
    <string name="email_empty_error_message">Email cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="email_error_message">Email is incorrect</string>
    <string name="password_not_match_error_message">Passwords do not match</string>
    <string name="connection_to_server_error_message">Connection error</string>
    <string name="invalid_credentials_error_message">Username or password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="reset_email_sent">Email sent</string>
    <string name="route_label">Route</string>
    <string name="weather_label">Weather</string>
    <string name="messages_label">Messages</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Open menu</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Close menu</string>
    <string name="nav_item_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="nav_item_edit_profile">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="nav_item_share">Share Pure Leagues</string>
    <string name="nav_item_about">About Pure Leagues</string>
    <string name="nav_item_terms">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="nav_item_privacy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="nav_item_contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="contact_tab_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="contact_us_reason_hint">Reason for contact</string>
    <string name="contact_us_name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="contact_us_email_hint">Email</string>
    <string name="contact_us_phone_hint">Telephone</string>
    <string name="contact_us_message_hint">Message</string>
    <string name="field_empty_error_message">Fill this field before submit</string>
    <string name="form_submitted_message">Form submitted</string>
    <string name="about_title">About Pure Leagues</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">About Pure Leagues</string>
    <string name="send_to">Send to</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_edit_text_view">edit profile</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_name_label">Name</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_age_label">Age</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_height_label">Height</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_weight_label">Weight</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_position_label">Position</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_save_text_view">save profile</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_profile_label">Profile</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_teams_label">Teams</string>
    <string name="welcome_add_team_button_text_button_text">add team</string>
    <string name="tab_edit_team_title">Edit team</string>
    <string name="shirt_colour_label">Shirt colour</string>
    <string name="edit_team_notifications_label">Notifications</string>
    <string name="edit_team_allow_notif_label">Allow notifications</string>
    <string name="delete_team_button_text">Delete team</string>
    <string name="delete_team_confirm_message">Are you sure you want to delete</string>
    <string name="delete_text">Delete</string>
    <string name="tables_games_label">P</string>
    <string name="tables_won_label">W</string>
    <string name="tables_drawn_label">D</string>
    <string name="tables_lost_label">L</string>
    <string name="tables_goals_for_label">F</string>
    <string name="tables_goals_against_label">A</string>
    <string name="tables_goals_difference_label">GD</string>
    <string name="tables_points_label">PTS</string>
    <string name="dashboard_fixture_versus_label">VS</string>
    <string name="dashboard_latest_messages_label">Latest messages</string>
    <string name="all_messages_button_text">Invite a Friend</string>
    <string name="yesterday_label">yesterday</string>
    <string name="today_label">today</string>
    <string name="edit_team_title">Edit team</string>
    <string name="unread_messages_pattern">Unread (%s)</string>
    <string name="weather_api_key">6deb2f98887cd3c4237c12480e3209a8</string>
    <string name="send_message_button_text">Post message</string>
    <string name="pick_image_dialog_text">Select Picture</string>
    <string name="statistics_goals">GOALS</string>
    <string name="statistics_top_scores">Top scorers</string>
    <string name="statistics_text_hint">Your club</string>
    <string name="results">Results</string>
    <string name="fixtures">Fixtures</string>
    <string name="statistics_spinner_prompt">Select your club</string>
    <string name="default_unread_messages">Unread (0)</string>
    <string name="nav_item_logout">Log out</string>
    <string name="no_fixtures_available">No fixtures available for %1$s</string>
    <string name="no_results_available">No results available for %1$s</string>
    <string name="close_text">Close</string>
    <string name="no_connection_message">No internet connection available</string>
    <string name="loading_data_message">Loading data…</string>
    <string name="max_teams_size_error_message">Max 3 teams allowed</string>
    <string name="max_manager_teams_size_error_message">Max 1 team allowed for manager</string>
    <string name="min_age_not_reached_error_message">You must be at least 13 years old</string>
    <string name="welcome_anonymous_login_button_text">anonymous login</string>
    <string name="register_error_message">You must register to use this feature</string>
    <string name="nav_item_register">Register</string>
    <string name="facebook_url">https://www.facebook.com/pureleagues</string>
    <string name="twitter_url">https://twitter.com/pureleagues</string>
    <string name="instagram_url">https://www.instagram.com/pureleagues</string>
    <string name="youtube_url">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCAEa9WxKzhh9Gi4pthtY8zw</string>
    <string name="snapchat_url">https://www.snapchat.com/add/pureleagues</string>
    <string name="admin_email">info@pureleagues.com</string>
    <string name="admin_password">F5R4E6E3m4a1n@</string>
    <string name="no_data_available">No data available</string>
    <string name="no_images_available">No images available</string>
    <string name="mailgun_domain">sandbox74833a22e5774355bd360c72bca70985.mailgun.org</string>
    <string name="mailgun_api_key">key-eb3b2416cb8b87332f3778c6834039cb</string>
    <string name="form_submitted_error_message">Service unavailable. Try again later.</string>
    <string name="submitting_text">Sending…</string>
    <string name="terms_text"><![CDATA[<p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Welcome!</strong></span></p> <p>We&rsquo;re thrilled you&rsquo;ve decided to use Pure Leagues and our other products and services, all of which we refer to simply as the &ldquo;Services&rdquo;.</p> <p>We&rsquo;ve drafted these Terms of Service (which we call the &ldquo;Terms&rdquo;) so you&rsquo;ll know the rules that govern our relationship with you. Although we have tried our best to strip the legalese from the Terms, there are places where these Terms may still read like a traditional contract. There&rsquo;s a good reason for that: these Terms do indeed form a legally binding contract between you and Pure Leagues. So please read them carefully.</p> <p>By using the Services, you agree to the Terms. Of course, if you don&rsquo;t agree with them, then don&rsquo;t use the Services.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>1. Who can use the services</strong></span></p> <p>No one under 13 is allowed to create an account or use the Services. We may offer additional Services with additional terms that may require you to be even older to use them. So please read all terms carefully.</p> <p>By using the Services, you state that:</p> <p>you can form a binding contract with Pure Leagues.</p> <p>you are not a person who is barred from receiving the Services under the laws of the United Kingdom, or any other applicable.</p> <p>you will comply with these Terms and all applicable to laws, rules and regulations.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>2. Rights we grant you</strong></span></p> <p>Pure Leagues grants you a personal, worldwide, royalty-free, non-assignable, non-exclusive, revocable and non-sublicensable licence to access and use the Services. This licence is for the sole purpose of letting you use and enjoy the Services&rsquo; benefits in a way that these Terms and our usage policies, such as our Community Guidelines, allow.</p> <p>Any software that we provide you may automatically download and install upgrades, updates, or other new features. You may be able to adjust these automatic downloads through your device&rsquo;s settings.</p> <p>You may not copy, modify, distribute, sell or lease any part of our Services. Nor may you reverse engineer or attempt to extract the source code of that software, unless laws prohibit these restrictions or you have our written permission to do so.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>3. Rights you grant us</strong></span></p> <p>Many of our Services let you create, upload, post, send, receive and store content. When you do that, you retain whatever ownership rights in that content you had to begin with. But you grant us a licence to use that content. How broad that licence is depends on which Services you use and the settings you have selected.</p> <p>For all Services other than Live, Local and any other crowd-sourced Service, you grant Pure Leagues and their affiliates a worldwide, royalty-free, sublicensable and transferable licence to host, store, use, display, reproduce, modify, adapt, edit, publish and distribute that content for as long as you use the Services. This licence is for the limited purpose of operating, developing, providing, promoting and improving the Services and researching and developing new ones.</p> <p>Because Live, Local and any other crowd-sourced Services are public by nature and record matters of public interest, the licence you grant us for content submitted to those Services is broader. In addition to granting us the rights mentioned in the previous paragraph, you also grant us a licence to create derivative works from, promote, exhibit, broadcast, syndicate, sublicence, publicly perform and publicly display content submitted to Live, Local or any other crowd-sourced Services in any form and in any and all media or distribution methods (now known or later developed). To the extent it&rsquo;s necessary, when you appear in, create, upload, post or send Live, Local or other crowd-sourced content, you also grant Pure Leagues and our affiliates and business partners the unrestricted, worldwide right and licence to use your name, likeness and voice. This means, among other things, that you will not be entitled to any compensation from Pure Leagues or our affiliates and business partners if your name, likeness or voice is conveyed through Live, Local or other crowd-sourced Services, either on the Pure Leagues application or on one of our business partners\' platforms.</p> <p>Though we&rsquo;re not required to do so, we may access, review, screen and delete your content at any time and for any reason, including if we think your content violates these Terms. However, you alone remain responsible for the content you create, upload, post, send or store through the Services.</p> <p>The Services may contain advertisements. In consideration for Pure Leagues letting you access and use the Services, you agree that we, our affiliates and our third-party partners may place advertising on the Services, including personalised advertising based upon the information you provide us or we collect or obtain about you. Because the Services contain content that you and other users provide us, advertising may sometimes appear near your content.</p> <p>We always love to hear from our users. But if you volunteer feedback or suggestions, just know that we can use your ideas without compensating you.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>4. The content of others</strong></span></p> <p>Much of the content on our Services is produced by users, publishers and other third parties. Whether that content is posted publicly or sent privately, the content is the sole responsibility of the person or organisation that submitted it. Although Pure Leagues reserves the right to review all content that appears on the Services and to remove any content that violates these Terms, we do not necessarily review all of it. So we can\'t &ndash; and don\'t &ndash; take responsibility for any content that others provide through the Services.</p> <p>Through these Terms and our Community Guidelines, we make clear that we don\'t want the Services to be put to bad uses. But because we don\'t review all content, we cannot guarantee that content on the Services will always conform to our Terms or Guidelines.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>5. Privacy</strong></span></p> <p>Your privacy matters to us. You can learn how your information is handled when you use our Services by reading the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to give the Privacy Policy a careful look because, by using our Services, you agree that your information may be collected and processed by Pure Leagues in the UK, as well as their affiliates, and transferred outside of the country in which you reside, including to countries that may not have the same data-protection laws as your country.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>6. Respecting other people&rsquo;s rights</strong></span></p> <p>Pure Leagues respects the rights of others. And so should you. You therefore may not use the Services in a manner that:</p> <p>violates or infringes someone else&rsquo;s rights of publicity, privacy, copyright, trademark or other intellectual-property right;</p> <p>bullies, harasses or intimidates;</p> <p>defames;</p> <p>spams or solicits our users.</p> <p>You must also respect the rights of Pure Leagues and its affiliates. These Terms do not grant you any right to:</p> <p>use branding, logos, designs, photographs, videos or any other materials used in our Services;</p> <p>copy, archive, download, upload, distribute, syndicate, broadcast, perform, display, make available or otherwise use any portion of the Services or the content on the Services except as set forth in these Terms;</p> <p>use the Services, any tools provided by the Services or any content on the Services for any commercial purposes without our consent.</p> <p>In short: you may not use the Services or the content on the Services in ways that are not authorised by these Terms. Nor may you help anyone else to do so.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>7. Respecting copyright</strong></span></p> <p>We respect copyright law. We therefore take reasonable steps to expeditiously remove from our Services any infringing material that we become aware of. And if Pure Leagues becomes aware that one of its users has repeatedly infringed copyrights, we will take reasonable steps within our power to terminate the user&rsquo;s account.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>8. Safety</strong></span></p> <p>We try hard to keep our Services a safe place for all users. But we can&rsquo;t guarantee it. That&rsquo;s where you come in. By using the Services, you agree that:</p> <p>You will not use the Services for any purpose that is illegal or prohibited in these Terms.</p> <p>You will not use any robot, spider, crawler, scraper or other automated means or interface to access the Services or extract other users\' information.</p> <p>You will not use or develop any third-party applications that interact with the Services or other users&rsquo; content or information without our written consent.</p> <p>You will not use the Services in a way that could interfere with, disrupt, affect negatively or inhibit other users from fully enjoying the Services or that could damage, disable, overburden or impair the functioning of the Services.</p> <p>You will not use or attempt to use another user&rsquo;s account, username or password without their permission.</p> <p>You will not solicit login credentials from another user.</p> <p>You will not post content that contains pornography, graphic violence, threats, hate speech or incitements to violence.</p> <p>You will not upload viruses or other malicious code or otherwise compromise the security of the Services.</p> <p>You will not attempt to circumvent any content-filtering techniques we employ or attempt to access areas or features of the Services that you are not authorised to access.</p> <p>You will not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of our Services or any system or network.</p> <p>You will not encourage or promote any activity that violates these Terms.</p> <p>We also care about your safety while using our Services. So do not use our Services in a way that would distract you from obeying traffic or safety laws. For example, never Snap and drive. And never put yourself or others in harm&rsquo;s way just to capture a Snap.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>9. Your account</strong></span></p> <p>You are responsible for any activity that occurs in your Pure Leagues account. So it&rsquo;s important that you keep your account secure. One way to do that is to select a strong password that you don&rsquo;t use for any other account.</p> <p>By using the Services, you agree that, in addition to exercising common sense:</p> <p>You will not create more than 1 account for yourself.</p> <p>You will not create another account if we have already disabled your account, unless you have our written permission to do so.</p> <p>You will not buy, sell, rent or lease access to your Pure Leagues account, Live, Snaps, a Pure Leagues username or a friend link without our written permission.</p> <p>You will not share your password.</p> <p>You will not log in or attempt to access the Services through unauthorised third-party applications or clients.</p> <p>If you think that someone has gained access to your account, please reach out immediately to Pure Leagues Support.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>10. Data charges and mobile phones</strong></span></p> <p>You are responsible for any mobile charges that you may incur for using our Services, including text messaging and data charges. If you&rsquo;re unsure what those charges may be, you should ask your service provider before using the Services.</p> <p>If you change or deactivate the mobile phone number that you used to create a Pure Leagues account, you must update your account information through Settings within 72 hours to prevent us from sending to someone else messages intended for you.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>12. Third-party services</strong></span></p> <p>If you use a service, feature or functionality that is operated by a third party and made available through our Services (including Services we offer jointly with the third party), each party&rsquo;s terms will govern the respective party&rsquo;s relationship with you. Neither Pure Leagues is responsible or liable for a third party&rsquo;s terms or actions taken under the third party&rsquo;s terms.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>13. Modifying the services and termination</strong></span></p> <p>We&rsquo;re relentlessly improving our Services and creating new ones all the time. This means that we may add or remove features, products or functionalities and we may also suspend or stop the Services altogether. We may take any of these actions at any time and, when we do, we will try to notify you beforehand &ndash; but this won\'t always be possible.</p> <p>Though we hope you remain a lifelong Pure Leagues user, you can terminate these Terms at any time and for any reason by deleting your account.</p> <p>Pure Leagues may also terminate these Terms with you at any time, for any reason. And while we&rsquo;ll try to give you advance notice, we can&rsquo;t guarantee it. Our right to terminate these Terms means that we may stop providing you with any Services, or impose new or additional limits on your ability to use the Services. For example, we may deactivate your account due to prolonged inactivity and we may reclaim your username at any time for any reason.</p> <p>Regardless of who terminates these Terms, both you and Pure Leagues continue to be bound by.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>14. Indemnity</strong></span></p> <p>You agree, to the extent permitted by law, to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Pure Leagues and our affiliates, directors, officers, stockholders, employees, licensors and agents from and against any complaints, charges, claims, damages, losses, costs, liabilities and expenses (including legal fees) due to, arising out of, or relating in any way to: (a) your access to or use of the Services; (b) your content; and (c) your breach of these Terms.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>15. Disclaimers</strong></span></p> <p>We try to keep the Services up and running and free of annoyances. But we make no promises that we will succeed.</p> <p>The Services are provided &ldquo;as is&rdquo; and &ldquo;as available&rdquo; and to the extent permitted by law without warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties, conditions, or other terms relating to merchantability, satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, title, quiet enjoyment, non-infringement, or arising from a course of dealing. In addition, while Pure Leagues attempts to provide a good user experience, we do not represent or warrant that: (a) the Services will always be secure, error-free or timely; (b) the Services will always function without delays, disruption or imperfections; or (c) that any content or information you obtain through the Services will be timely or accurate.</p> <p>Pure Leagues and their affiliates take no responsibility and assume no liability for any content that you, another user or a third party creates, uploads, posts, sends, receives or stores on or through our Services. You understand and agree that you may be exposed to content that might be offensive, illegal, misleading or otherwise inappropriate, none of which Pure Leagues, . nor their affiliates will be responsible for.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>16. Limitation of liability</strong></span></p> <p>When permitted by law, Pure Leagues and our affiliates, directors, officers, stockholders, employees, licensors and agents will not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, punitive or multiple damages, or any loss of profits or revenues, whether incurred directly or indirectly, or any loss of data, use, goodwill or other intangible losses, resulting from: (a) your use of the Services or inability to use the Services; (b) your access to or inability to access the Services; (c) the conduct or content of other users or third parties on or through the Services; or (d) unauthorised access, use or alteration of your content, even if Pure Leagues has been advised of the possibility of such damages. In no event will Pure Leagues, . or their affiliates&rsquo; aggregate liability for all claims relating to the Services exceed the greater of &pound;100 GBP or the amount you paid Pure Leagues, if any, in the last 12 months.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES, SO SOME OR ALL OF THE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS IN THIS SECTION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.</strong></span></p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>17. Dispute resolution and arbitration</strong></span></p> <p>If you have a concern, let&rsquo;s talk. Go ahead and contact us first and we&rsquo;ll do our best to resolve the issue.</p> <p>Some of our Services may have additional terms that contain dispute-resolution provisions unique to that Service or your residency.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>18. Exclusive venue</strong></span></p> <p>To the extent the parties are permitted under these Terms to initiate litigation in a court, both you and Pure Leagues agree that all claims and disputes (whether contractual or otherwise) arising out of or relating to the Terms or the use of the Services will be litigated exclusively in the courts of England in the United Kingdom, unless this is prohibited by the laws of the country where you reside. You and Pure Leagues consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of those courts.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>19. Choice of law</strong></span></p> <p>The laws of England and Wales govern these Terms and any claims and disputes (whether contractual or otherwise) arising out of or relating to these Terms or their subject matter. The courts in some countries may not apply the laws of England and Wales to some disputes related to these Terms. If you reside in one of those countries, the laws of your home country may apply to those disputes.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>20. Severability</strong></span></p> <p>If any provision of these Terms is found unenforceable, then that provision will be severed from these Terms and not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>21. Additional terms for specific Services</strong></span></p> <p>Given the breadth of our Services, we sometimes need to craft additional terms and conditions for specific Services. Those additional terms and conditions, which will be available with the relevant Services, then become part of your agreement with us if you use those Services. If any part of those additional terms and conditions conflicts with these Terms, the additional terms and conditions will prevail.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>22. Final terms</strong></span></p> <p>These Terms (together with any additional terms applicable to specific Services you use) make up the entire agreement between you and Pure Leagues and supersede any prior agreements.</p> <p>These Terms do not create or confer any third-party beneficiary rights.</p> <p>If we do not enforce a provision in these Terms, it will not be considered a waiver.</p> <p>We reserve all rights not expressly granted to you.</p> <p>You may not transfer any of your rights or obligations under these Terms without our consent.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Contact us</strong></span></p> <p>Pure Leagues welcomes comments, questions, concerns or suggestions. You can send us feedback or get support by using Contact Us within the app form.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p>]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_text"><![CDATA[<p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Privacy Policy</strong></span></p> <p>Last Modified: May 25, 2017</p> <p>Pure Leagues is a fast and fun way to share experiences with your friends and the world around you. You can send a photo or video to friends, chronicle your day through Story, touch base using Pure Leagues</p> <p>When you use these services&mdash;and any others we in the Pure Leagues, whether in the Pure Leagues app or elsewhere&mdash;you&rsquo;ll share some information with us. We get that that can affect your privacy. So we want to be upfront about the information we collect, how we use it, whom we share it with, and the choices we give you to control, access, and update your information.</p> <p>That&rsquo;s why we&rsquo;ve written this Privacy Policy. And it&rsquo;s why we&rsquo;ve tried to write it in a way that&rsquo;s blissfully free of the legalese that often clouds these documents. Of course, if you still have questions about anything in our Privacy Policy, just contact us.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Information We Collect</strong></span></p> <p>There are three basic categories of information we collect:</p> <p>&bull;Information you choose to give us.<br /> &bull;Information we get when you use our services.<br /> &bull;Information we get from third parties.</p> <p>Here&rsquo;s a little more detail on each of these categories.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Information You Choose to Give Us</strong></span></p> <p>When you interact with our services, we collect the information that you choose to share with us. For example, most of our services require you to set up a basic Pure Leagues account, so we need to collect a few important details about you, such as: a unique username you&rsquo;d like to go by, a password, an email address, a phone number, and your date of birth. To make it easier for others to find you, we may also ask you to provide us with some additional information that will be publicly visible on our services, such as profile pictures, a name, or other useful identifying information.</p> <p>Of course, you&rsquo;ll also provide us whatever information you send through the services. Keep in mind that the users you send messages to in Pure Leagues and any other content to can always save that content or copy it outside the app. So, the same common sense that applies to the internet at large applies to Pure Leagues as well: Don&rsquo;t send messages or share content that you wouldn&rsquo;t want someone to save or share.</p> <p>It probably goes without saying, but we&rsquo;ll say it anyway: When you contact Pure Leagues or communicate with us in any other way, we&rsquo;ll collect whatever information you volunteer.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Information We Get When You Use Our Services</strong></span></p> <p>When you use our services, we collect information about which of those services you&rsquo;ve used and how you&rsquo;ve used them. We might know, for instance, that you watched a particular match, saw a specific ad for a certain period of time, and sent a few messages to friends. Here&rsquo;s a fuller explanation of the types of information we collect when you use our services:</p> <p>Usage Information. We collect information about your activity through our services. For example, we may collect information about:</p> <p>how you interact with the services, such as which filters you view or apply to Pure Leagues.</p> <p>how you communicate with other Pure League users, such as their names, the time and date of your communications, the number of messages you exchange with your friends, which friends you exchange messages with the most, and your interactions with messages.</p> <p>Content Information. We collect information about the content you provide, such as if the recipient has viewed the content and the metadata that is provided with the content.</p> <p>Device Information. We collect device-specific information, such as the hardware model, operating system version, advertising identifier, unique application identifiers, unique device identifiers, browser type, language, wireless network, and mobile network information (including the mobile phone number).</p> <p>Device Phonebook. Because Pure Leagues is all about communicating with friends, we may&mdash;with your consent&mdash;collect information from your device&rsquo;s phonebook.</p> <p>Camera and Photos. Many of our services require us to collect images and other information from your device&rsquo;s camera and photos. For example, you won&rsquo;t be able to send Pure Leagues or upload photos from your camera roll unless we can access your camera or photos.</p> <p>Location Information. When you use our services we may collect information about your location. With your consent, we may also collect information about your precise location using methods that include GPS, wireless networks, cell towers, Wi-Fi access points, and other sensors, such as gyroscopes, accelerometers, and compasses.</p> <p>Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies. Like most online services and mobile applications, we may use cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons, web storage, and unique advertising identifiers, to collect information about your activity, browser, and device. We may also use these technologies to collect information when you interact with services we offer through one of our partners, such as commerce features. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually remove or reject browser cookies through the settings on your browser or device. Keep in mind, though, that removing or rejecting cookies could affect the availability and functionality of our services. To learn more about how we use cookies and your choices, please check out our Cookie Statement. To learn more about how third parties use these technologies on our services, be sure to read the Analytics and Advertising Services Provided by Others section of our Privacy Policy.</p> <p>Log Information. We also collect log information when you use our app. That information includes, among other things:</p> <p>&bull;details about how you&rsquo;ve used our services.<br /> &bull;device information, such as your web browser type and language.<br /> &bull;access times.<br /> &bull;pages viewed.<br /> &bull;IP address.<br /> &bull;identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser.</p> <p>pages you visited before or after navigating to our website.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Information We Collect from Third Parties</strong></span></p> <p>We may collect information that other users provide about you when they use our services. For example, if another user allows us to collect information from their device phonebook&mdash;and you&rsquo;re one of that user&rsquo;s contacts&mdash;we may combine the information we collect from that user&rsquo;s phonebook with other information we have collected about you. We may also obtain information from other companies that are owned or operated by us, or any other third-party sources, and combine that with the information we collect through our services.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>How We Use Information</strong></span></p> <p>What do we do with the information we collect? The short answer is: Provide you with an amazing set of products and services that we relentlessly improve. Here are some of the ways we do that:</p> <p>&bull;develop, operate, improve, deliver, maintain, and protect our products and services.<br> &bull;send you communications, including by email. For example, we may use email to respond to support inquiries or to share information about our products, services, and promotional offers that we think may interest you.<br> &bull;monitor and analyze trends and usage.<br> &bull;personalize the services by, among other things, suggesting friends or profile information, or customizing the content we show you, including ads.<br> &bull;contextualize your experience by, among other things, tagging your Memories content using your precise location data (if, of course, you&rsquo;ve consented to us collecting that data) and applying other labels based on the content.<br> &bull;improve ad targeting and measurement, including through the use of your precise location data (again, if you&rsquo;ve consented to us collecting that data). See the Control Over Your Information section below for more information about Pure Leagues Inc.&rsquo;s advertising practices and your choices.<br> &bull;enhance the safety and security of our products and services.<br> &bull;verify your identity and prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity.<br> &bull;use information we&rsquo;ve collected from cookies and other technology to enhance the services and your experience with them.<br> &bull;enforce our Terms of Service and other usage policies.</p> <p>We may also store some information locally on your device. For example, we may store information as local cache so that you can open the app and view content faster.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>How We Share Information</strong></span></p> <p>We may share information about you in the following ways:</p> <p>&bull;We may share the following information with other Pure Leagues users.<br /> &bull;information about you, such as your username, name, and nickname.<br /> &bull;information about how you have interacted with the services, such as your Pure Leagues &ldquo;score,&rdquo; the names of Pure League users you are friends with, and other information that will help Pure League users understand your connections with others using the services. For example, because it may not be clear whether a new friend request comes from someone you actually know, we may share whether you and the requestor have Pure Leagues friends in common.<br /> &bull;any additional information you have consented for us to share. For example, when you let us access your device phonebook, we may share information about you with other users who have your phone number in their device phonebook.<br /> &bull;content you post or send will be shared with other Pure League users</p> <p>With all Pure Leagues users, our business partners, and the general public. We may share the following information with all Pure League users as well as with our business partners and the general public:</p> <p>&bull;public information like your name, username, Pure League user and profile pictures.</p> <p>&bull;any content that you submit to Live, Local, or any other crowd-sourced service. If a Live, Local, or any other crowd-sourced service is streamed on the web or broadcast in some other media, it may be viewed by the public at large or rebroadcast by our business partners.</p> <p>With our affiliates. We may share information with entities within the Pure Leagues Inc. family of companies.</p> <p>With third parties. We may share your information with the following third parties:</p> <p>With service providers, sellers, and partners. We may share information about you with service providers who perform services on our behalf, sellers that provide goods through our services, and business partners that provide services and functionality.</p> <p>With third parties for legal reasons. We may share information about you if we reasonably believe that disclosing the information is needed to:</p> <p>&bull;comply with any valid legal process, governmental request, or applicable law, rule, or regulation.<br /> &bull;investigate, remedy, or enforce potential Terms of Service violations.<br /> &bull;protect the rights, property, and safety of us, our users, or others.<br /> &bull;detect and resolve any fraud or security concerns.</p> <p>With third parties as part of a merger or acquisition. If Pure Leagues Inc. gets involved in a merger, asset sale, financing, liquidation or bankruptcy, or acquisition of all or some portion of our business to another company, we may share your information with that company before and after the transaction closes.</p> <p>We may also share with third parties&mdash;such as advertisers&mdash;aggregated, non-personally identifiable, or de-identified information.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Third-Party Content and Integrations</strong></span></p> <p>The services may also contain third-party links and search results, include third-party integrations, or offer a co-branded or third-party-branded service. Through these links, third-party integrations, and co-branded or third-party-branded services, you may be providing information (including personal information) directly to the third party, us, or both. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for how those third parties collect or use your information. As always, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of every third-party website or service that you visit or use, including those third parties you interact with through our services.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Analytics and Advertising Services Provided by Others</strong></span></p> <p>We may let other companies use cookies, web beacons, and similar tracking technologies on our services. These companies may collect information about how you use our services and other websites and online services over time and across different services. This information may be used to, among other things, analyse and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand your online activity.</p> <p>Additionally, some companies may use information collected on our services to deliver targeted advertisements on behalf of us or other companies, including on third-party websites and apps. For more information about interest-based ads and the choices available to you, go here.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Children</strong></span></p> <p>Our services are not intended for&mdash;and we don&rsquo;t direct them to&mdash;anyone under 13. And that&rsquo;s why we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13.</p> <p><span style=\"color: #000000;\"><strong>Revisions to the Privacy Policy</strong></span></p> <p>We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. But when we do, we&rsquo;ll let you know one way or another. Sometimes, we&rsquo;ll let you know by revising the date at the top of the Privacy Policy that&rsquo;s available on our website and mobile application. Other times, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our websites&rsquo; homepages or providing you with an in-app notification).</p>]]></string>

    <string name="url_to_report_begin" formatted="false">http://dashboard-env.3ckhcpskac.us-east-1.elasticbeanstalk.com/apps/Pure%20Leagues/browser/Message?filters=%5B%7B%22field%22%3A%22objectId%22%2C%22constraint%22%3A%22eq%22%2C%22compareTo%22%3A%22</string>
    <string name="url_to_report_end" formatted="false">%22%7D%5D</string>
    <string name="ok_button">Ok</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="report_abuse">Report Abuse</string>
    <string name="report_submitted_message">Report received and submitted</string>
    <string name="report_submitted_error_message">Service unavailable. Try again later.</string>
    <string name="report_dialog_message">Do you really want to report user \"%1$s\"</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="login_in_message">Login...</string>
    <string name="sending_email_message">Sending email...</string>
    <string name="deleting_message">Deleting...</string>
    <string name="logout_message">Logout..</string>
    <string name="registering_message">Loading...</string>
    <string name="registering_user_message">Registering...</string>
    <string name="division_select_message">Please, select division</string>
    <string name="club_select_message">Please, select club</string>
    <string name="team_colours_select_message">Please, select team colours</string>
    <string name="accuweather_api_key">XTSiBsX2qHTOpYx85DfGQIJWM07STLyK</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="route_dialog_title">Please enter required information</string>
    <string name="town_of_match">Town of match</string>
    <string name="venue_of_match">Venue of match</string>
    <string name="about_pure_leagues" formatted="false"><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #000000 ;"><strong>About us</strong></span></p>Follow your own football team as a player or supporter with this free app, get information about your team\'s fixtures and results and keep up on the latest news relating to your league or team with messaging.
   <ol>
       <li>Follow up to three teams</li>
       <li>Set your own strip for easy identification of team</li>
           <li>See upcoming  fixtures</li>
               <li>Match results and league tables</li>
                   <li>Statistics on players</li>
                       <li>Post messages, photos and comment on upcoming or previous matches</li>
                           <li>Picture Gallery</li>
                               <li>Weather forecasts</li>
                                   <li>Directions to your next match</li>
   </ol>
   <p>This is Pure leagues first release and we have more releases planned which will help administrators, managers, players and supporters to get more involved, and if you have ideas on what would be good to have in Pure Leagues, let us know.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="post">POST</string>

    <string-array name="genders">
        <item>@string/male_item</item>
        <item>@string/female_item</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="user_types">
        <item>@string/player_item</item>
        <item>@string/manager_item</item>
        <item>@string/referee_item</item>
        <item>@string/family_member_item</item>
        <item>@string/follower_item</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="io.branch.apiKey" translatable="false">key_live_mitq835A45CbSw42LIMyAomczyd1y43d</string>
    <string name="branch_share_link">Check out this awesome new app; follow your team’s fixtures, results, league tables, instant messaging and lots more, for players, team managers and supporters.
Click on link below to download Pure League FREE app…….\nhttps://e6m2.app.link/JCbrRgPH3F</string>
    <string name="username_contains_spaces_error_message">Username cannot include spaces</string>
    <string name="take_photo">Take photo</string>
    <string name="choose_photo">Choose photo</string>
</resources>
